Hello.
こんにちは
こんちは
What do you think?
どうですかね?
Are you nervous?
緊張してますか?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I don't know a lot of things yet, so is it okay if I ask you a lot of questions?
まだいろいろ分からないから、いろいろ質問しても大丈夫?
yes.
はい
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今って、彼氏さんとかっているんですか?
yes.
はい
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんですね
What kind of person are you?
どういう方なのか?
Well, Yankee Chick.
えー、ヤンキーチックの
Oh, do you have a Yankee-like feel?
あ、ヤンキーチックな感じなんですか?
Wow, that's kind of surprising.
へー、意外ですね、なんか
Where did you meet your boyfriend?
それを彼氏さんとはどこで知り合ったんですか?
I was picked up.
ナンパされました
Oh, are you picking up girls?
あー、ナンパっすか?
Are you going to pick up girls or something?
ナンパとかついていっちゃうんすか?
So what was your type?
じゃあタイプだった?
It was the type.
タイプだった
Hey, that's right.
へー、そうなんだ
It was like I picked her up and started dating him.
ナンパして付き合ったみたいな感じだった
Did you have sex that day?
それはその日にエッチしちゃったの?
No, I haven't.
いやー、してないです
How did you feel, you asked?
どんな感じでさ、聞かれたの?
So did you get asked through your contact information?
じゃあ連絡先で聞かれたの?
I declined, but the next time we met again,
断ったんですけど、次の時また会って、
It was given to me at that time.
その時に渡されて
Oh, what's your contact information?
あ、連絡先を?
It's not like we met on the street, right?
それは街で会ったとかじゃないっしょ?
Oh, I got picked up at my part-time job.
あ、バイト先でナンパされて
Ah, I have a part-time job, that's right.
あー、バイト先なんだ、そうなんだ、
I see.
なるほどね
But it appealed to me.
でもアピールされたんだ
So, that's right, how are you now that you're dating?
で、そうなんだ、付き合って、今どうですか?
Do you like your boyfriend?
彼氏さんのこと好きですか?
Yeah.
うん
Eh?
えー?
Fair enough.
まあまあ
Is it okay?
まあまあっすか?
Are there any other good people?
他にいい人いるんですか?
No, I'm not there.
いやー、いないです
So, did you have sex with your boyfriend recently?
じゃあ彼氏さんと最近エッチしました?
Yes, I did.
うん、しました
When did you have sex?
いつエッチしました?
1 week ago.
1週間前
So aren't you in love?
じゃあラブラブじゃないですか?
What about having sex with your boyfriend?
どうなんすか、彼氏さんとのエッチは?
Do you like sex in the first place?
そもそもエッチ好きですか?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I don't dislike it.
まあ、嫌いではない
まあ、嫌いではないと
What do you think? Are you satisfied with having sex with your boyfriend?
どうですか、彼氏さんとエッチ満足してます?
usually.
普通
Is it normal?
普通っすか?
Eh.
えー
So, are there any Sephires now?
じゃあ今セフィレとかいるんですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
Have you been there before?
昔いたりしたの?
No, it's not there.
いや、いないです
real?
ほんと?
That's right.
そうなんだ
I see, I see.
そ っかそっか、なるほどね
So, then that's it.
ってことは、じゃああれだね
I mean, I like sex.
エッチは好きってことね
What kind of sex do you like?
どういうエッチが好きとかありますか?
Forcible.
強引な
Are you pretty M?
結構Mなんすか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Hey M.
ちょっとM
Please tell me the X of M.
MのXを教えてくださいよ
Eh.
えー
It's a secret.
内緒です
secret?
内緒?
REASONS
OKOK
Well then, just tell me how to touch it.
じゃあ、触りだけ教えてね
Just touch?
触りだけ?
Like getting hit.
叩かれるのとか
I don't dislike it, that much.
それ嫌いじゃないんだ、あんまり
Where did you get hit?
どこ叩かれたりしたの?
Butt?
お尻とか?
Butt.
お尻
In the end, it's M, surprisingly.
結局Mなんだね、意外にね
Eh, I see.
えー、そっか
Well, when it comes to sex, what kind of body do you like?
なんか、エッチはさ、どういう体が好きとかあるの?
Is it back?
バックですか?
Oh, I like the back.
あ、バックが好きなんだ
Well, I like the feeling of being fucked unexpectedly from deep inside.
じゃあ、意外に奥からやられる感じとか好きなんだ
Hmm, that's surprising.
うーん、意外っすね
I can't even say that I feel that way.
なんか、そんな感じも言えないですけどね
Hahahaha, is that so?
はははは、そうなんですか
Eh.
えー
At first glance, it looks like a woman.
一目だけに女いっすね
Your smile is cute.
笑顔かわいいっすね
Do men always compliment you on certain parts?
男の人に、なんか、どこパーツ褒められてします?
Hmm.
うーん
But the smile...
でも、笑顔は...
Yeah, sure.
うんうん、確かにね
Her eyes are big too.
目も大きいしね
Black hair suits you too.
黒髪も似合ってるよね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Where do you get compliments about your body?
体とかとか、どこ褒められたりするの?
Eh.
えー
Is it your butt?
お尻とかですか?
Butt?
お尻?
Please let me take a closer look at it a little later.
ちょっと後でそれじっくり見させてください
Hmm, where do you find sensuality?
う ーん、なんか性感とかどこだったりするの?
Eh.
えー
For example, ears, neck, etc.
例えば耳とかさ、首すちとかさ
Ears?
耳とか?
I like ears.
耳は好き
Do you like listening?
耳好きなんすか?
What is that?
それはどうなんすか?
Do you like being touched?
触られるのが好きなんすか?
Being touched...
触られて...
Do you like being licked?
舐められるのが好きなんすか?
I like being touched.
触られるのが好きです
To.
へ ー
I like being touched.
触 られるのが好きなん
Do you?
す か?
What about the neck?
首すちとかどうすか?
I like it.
好きです
Oh, do you like it?
あ、好きなんすか?
Yeah.
うん
Did it tickle?
くすぐった?
What does it feel like to be tickled?
くすぐった気持ちって感じ?
May I touch you for a moment?
一瞬触っちゃおうかな?
Did it tickle your feet too?
ここ足とかもくすぐったかな?
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
My feet are ticklish.
足くすぐったいんだ
Just once, try standing up.
一回さ、軽く立ってみて
Look closely.
くちぐち見て
So cute.
かわいいっすね
Again, put your feet on the sofa and try being a MT.
またさ、 ソファーの上にさ、足乗せてMTになってみて
Can you come a little closer?
もうちょい手前来れる?
Again, try spreading the mango with both hands.
またさ、自分でさ、 マンゴー両手で広げてみて
Try making it with both hands.
両手作ってみて
It's good.
よがていです